[Music]
[音乐]
这是关于如何制作狮子卡
this is about how to make a lion card
这对生日很好，所以这
是基于的生日狮子卡
this is about how to make a lion card
which is very good for birthdays so this
弯曲的形状，这是我教程13
这里有一些预切的东西
which is very good for birthdays so this
is a birthday lion card it's based on
他们的尺寸使一个
完全像这样，您实际上可以做到
is a birthday lion card it's based on
curved shapes which is tutorial 13 I've
通过眼睛，在这种情况下，您可能会得到
您可能想要的形状略有不同
curved shapes which is tutorial 13 I've
got some pre-cut pieces here with all
玩，但如果你想
就是这样一个是上颚
got some pre-cut pieces here with all
the dimensions on them to make one
这是下颚，所以
尺寸是这里的长度
the dimensions on them to make one
exactly like this you can actually do it
沿这是八，所以这是
这个长度八厘米，这里八
exactly like this you can actually do it
by eye in which case you might get
厘米，然后你来到这里
这是六厘米，然后是
by eye in which case you might get
slightly different shapes you might want
另外六厘米，你需要三个
选项卡两个一个去这里，一个去这里
slightly different shapes you might want
to play around with it but if you want
它将粘贴到页面上，然后
这个是拉动整体的一个
to play around with it but if you want
one just like this this is the top jaw
形状变成卡片
调整角度
one just like this this is the top jaw
and this is the bottom jaw and so the
页面和这个中央折痕是
您所到之处的角度为65度
and this is the bottom jaw and so the
dimensions are the length along here
围绕曲线折叠
鼻子的弯曲是一百
dimensions are the length along here
along here this is eight so this is
三十度的制作方法
就是这样折成两半
along here this is eight so this is
eight centimeters this length here eight
然后您可以测量这130和
那么你只剪掉一侧
eight centimeters this length here eight
centimeters and then you come up here
在另一边留下标签
在教程中解释了十三弯
centimeters and then you come up here
this is six centimeters and then this is
形状这是下颚，所以这
实际上会像这样坚持
this is six centimeters and then this is
another six centimeters you need three
这种情况下沿着底部的长度
下巴贴在这里
another six centimeters you need three
tabs two one goes here and one goes here
佩奇是9厘米，这有点
它出现在这里的是6
tabs two one goes here and one goes here
which will stick it to the page and then
厘米
这实际上是一个锐角v-fold
which will stick it to the page and then
this one is the one that pulls the whole
这是教程2，这是基础
从您所在的位置下降
this one is the one that pulls the whole
thing into shape to make it into a card
会黏住5个上颚
厘米从
thing into shape to make it into a card
shape the angles the angles here between
底部，你要坚持这个
一下来就是一个半
shape the angles the angles here between
the page and this central crease that is
厘米，然后是所有角度
你把它放下和中央
the page and this central crease that is
65 degrees the angle here where you go
脊柱都是35度，所以我
只需将其粘贴到此处，即可
65 degrees the angle here where you go
around the curve the fold goes around
只是看看它的样子，因为
我测量过，你实际上可以坚持所有
around the curve the fold goes around
the curve of the nose that's a hundred
我会同时贴标签
丹通常伸出来，我们坚持下来
the curve of the nose that's a hundred
and thirty degrees so well way of making
一侧折叠将其关闭，将胶水粘在
另一边折叠整个底座
and thirty degrees so well way of making
it is you just fold it in half like this
封闭，所以他们找到了自己的自然地方
但在这种情况下，因为这就是全部
it is you just fold it in half like this
and then you can measure this 130 and
测量我们可以将两面都朝下
同一时间
and then you can measure this 130 and
then you've just cut out one side and
那是第一个，只是为了
确定听起来我们会关闭它
then you've just cut out one side and
leave a tab on the other side it's all
如果我的测量值有点狡猾，是的
所以那是下颚上颚
leave a tab on the other side it's all
explained in tutorials thirteen curved
首先将其粘上，这样您就可以
圆角的形状，所以我们只需在上面涂胶
explained in tutorials thirteen curved
shapes this is the bottom jaw so this
轻轻地将胶水涂抹到
折痕很重要
shapes this is the bottom jaw so this
will actually stick on like this and in
粘贴时将其折叠关闭
应该完全能够
will actually stick on like this and in
this case the length along the bottom
平，所以我们可以再坚持一次
这些行，我们可以在两个标签上粘贴
this case the length along the bottom
jaw here where it sticks
同时我会把它转过来
所以我实际上可以从
jaw here where it sticks
Paige that's 9 centimeters and this bit
里面，所以再次在这两个上面放胶
直到折痕是
Paige that's 9 centimeters and this bit
where it comes up here that's 6
重要的事情如此卡住
线，我将其关闭
where it comes up here that's 6
centimeters
确保一切顺利，这是
您的基本头型使用弯曲
centimeters
this is actually an acute angle v-fold
我将尺寸留在了
在这种情况下在外面，但通常这样做
this is actually an acute angle v-fold
that's tutorial 2 here's the base so
用铅笔擦掉或粘
他们放在里面，然后你如何
that's tutorial 2 here's the base so
coming down from the top where you're
装饰取决于你，所以如果你看
在这头狮子的鬃毛上，这些都是
coming down from the top where you're
going to stick the top jaw that's 5
只是已经切出的扁平片
坚持下去，但您可能会选择
going to stick the top jaw that's 5
centimeters here coming up from the
实际在这里或某些类型的耳朵
粗糙或某种花哨的衣领或
centimeters here coming up from the
bottom where you're going to stick this
这样的东西
眼睛只是已经
bottom where you're going to stick this
one down that's one and a half
卡在牙齿上，这些只是碎片
卡在边缘和
one down that's one and a half
centimeters and then all the angles
舌头和鼻子都只是
这些其他贴在耳朵上的东西
centimeters and then all the angles
where you stick it down and the central
小耳件，它们只是
只是卡住了简单
where you stick it down and the central
spine they're all 35 degrees so I've
没有什么可以解释的，只是
您可以根据自己的需要来设计
spine they're all 35 degrees so I've
just stick this onto here so you can
您想要两个钳口的方式
因为它们是v形折叠，指向
just stick this onto here so you can
just see how it's going to look because
相反的方向
v形折叠方向向下
just see how it's going to look because
I measured it you can actually stick all
他们指出，所以在这里我们有一个
指向页面和一个指向
I measured it you can actually stick all
the tabs at the same time I'll stick and
向下移动页面，使其关闭
相反的方向
the tabs at the same time I'll stick and
Dan sticking out normally we stick down
打开下巴，所以在这里我们可以
看着狮子，你可以看到顶部和
Dan sticking out normally we stick down
one sides fold it closed put glue on the
狮子的下颚在你mp缩时
打开和关闭它，所以这是狮子
one sides fold it closed put glue on the
other side and fold the whole base
可以改编成的生日贺卡
各种各样的其他生物
other side and fold the whole base
closed so they find their natural place
您
[音乐]
closed so they find their natural place
but in this case because it's all